hey what's up everybody thanks for
listening to The Grow Your Life podcast
my name is Jeremy microkowski and today
I'm going to be talking about something
I think is an Urgent Message that people
need to hear and this comes because you
know I've been working in the coaching
industry for two decades and I see
people take way longer than they need to
to actually accomplish things and most
people only need about 30 days to
actually reach their goal the problem is
I see and this is no exaggeration people
taking five to ten years to finally get
to the place where they take 30 days to
actually do the thing that they want to
do in their business and so what if
instead of it taking you five to ten
years to finally gain the courage to put
your stuff out there to launch something
you actually did it right away and so
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
help you with that right now I'm going
to help you answer a few questions that
maybe you have that I have had you stuck
one of the biggest ones that people have
is what's a topic that's profitable and
here's the biggest thing I'm going to
say that's going to help do with this
not all information
works for a mentorship business not all
information is going to be profitable
for you to launch out there now this
this right here is a big reason why most
people usually struggle to launch is
because they're waiting until they have
certainty and confidence that what
they're going to put out there is going
to work for them and that's the worst
thing that you can do
the worst thing that you can do is wait
until you know for sure that it's going
to work out and that it's a good idea to
Launch
I'm going to say that again the worst
thing that you can do is to wait until
you know for sure that it's going to
work out and that what you've picked to
do is going to work I see people do this
they toss around five to ten different
ideas for a niche but they haven't quite
picked one yet and they haven't quite
launched and ultimately it's because
they're they're coming up with reasons
why their brain is focused on all the
ways that it can go wrong for them
instead of having hope for how it can go
right and being willing to experiment
and put themselves out there and be okay
with it failing be okay with just seeing
what happens this right here
is what stops people makes them take 10
years
to do anything at the core of it
is you gotta just accept the risk
and put something out there now here's
how we can mitigate this risk okay
is
people will pay for a transformation
that they desire
that will take them from where they are
to where they want to be okay just
because you have information to give
people people are not going to just pay
for information I see people why did
nobody buy my art therapy why did nobody
buy my stories things like that like
that is you trying to get people to buy
into your creativity that's not you
actually bringing a transformation to
somebody and walking them through a
process that's going to help them and so
the first thing is is that people invest
in mentorship in coaching in training
when they feel confident that it's going
to produce an end result outcome for
them if you have no idea about what you
could deliver to people to bring an end
result outcome to them
that's where you need to start to study
and figure that out but you don't need
to take a long time to do that okay we
all have experiences we all have
knowledge we all have things that we can
help people with we can also learn and
grow in certain areas
but what's not going to help is you over
analyzing coming up with all the ways
that it could not work out and then not
testing something out
what you want to pay attention to is
this is that whatever you put out there
in a mentorship in a coaching business
it needs to not just be information
about something okay about how to do
something or or just information in
general it needs to be connected with
a framework for how you actually help
people do that themselves
information is useless to people because
it's very difficult for most people to
translate information
into taking action in their life
it's very difficult for most people and
so your goal is to actually create
the journey for them to walk people
through a journey to where you're
guiding people and leading people
to take an outcome this is why
if you're so concerned about people
liking you approving of you liking your
content like you won't make money in
this business you won't
okay
what will make you money is being
willing to test experiment and discover
what are the transformational goals that
people in your space want and how can
you guide them there how can you take
them to that result
now here's the other thing too I hear a
lot of people say this
I'm just setting the foundations for my
business I'm getting stuff together I'm
getting things in order and and and that
is
a lie it is
because people who are actually doing
the work don't say that they're getting
things in order they just do the work
and so whatever you have come up with
and I used to do this same thing myself
and I understand that this is offensive
to you
I'm talking from my own experience here
I was lying about what I was actually
preparing for
what I was actually doing was
disassociating
I was distracting myself it was too
painful to look at why I wasn't taking
action my biggest reason was I said I
have too much work to do I don't have
enough time I don't have enough energy
to build the business that I want and as
soon as I decided to no longer buy into
that lie our business has made 850 000
in the last 11 months okay
and so you have to understand
that there comes a moment and it's
usually a 30-day 60-day spark where you
finally start moving and taking momentum
and you're and and you let go of being
concerned if things actually will work
out that's one of the biggest things is
when you finally let go of the concern
of is this going to work out are people
going to connect with us will this
produce a result when you legitimately
let go of that that's where the spark of
Genius comes from
and that's where I've seen people make
so much more money okay and so
you might come up with a thousand and
one reasons why you can't maybe your
personality doesn't doesn't fit into
that mold whatever
in today's world with artificial
intelligence
you don't have the luxury and time
anymore
of sitting on an idea for months at a
time because if you sit on an idea
and I've seen this happen
for six 12 24 months
a thousand other people will have
already had that idea that you had
and exhausted the marketplace with it
and now by the time you put it out there
it's not going to work and then this
becomes this self-fulfilling prophecy of
by the time I get things up it never
works by the time you know nothing ever
works out for me well
when we can actually learn to once we
have the spark of the idea we don't
second guess it we don't question it
we start to move on our instincts we
start to move on our intuition instead
of wondering is this a good idea we take
action even if it doesn't pan out how we
would hope it to
that behavior will pay you dividends
more than anything else
and and whatever you gotta do to get to
that place I would do as quickly as
possible
you might need to talk with a therapist
you might need to work on whatever
triggers are actually stopping you from
taking action
we have to become self-aware of why
we are taking longer than 30 days to
launch our offers why we are unwilling
to experiment and see
how just how things go
put something out there oh and by the
way experiment if it fails you need to
then do it again
tweak it adjust it not sit on The
Laurels of oh well this didn't work out
now we're going to sit on it for six
months no
sit on it for 30 days and then go again
okay I I I know that I've I've been
talking for a while from this
perspective of
of have self-compassion and
self-acceptance and that's so important
to do
but on the flip side we have to be
disciplined to actually act on our ideas
move things forward instead of sitting
around waiting for Perfection waiting
until we feel good about it here's a
hint
in this industry in the mentorship in
the coaching industry you will never
feel
good about
anything you launch let me explain that
there will never come a time and I say
this from experience because I've worked
with the top mentors there will never
actually come a time where you feel good
enough about your offer that you feel
okay I can finally have the confidence
to put it out there never that day never
actually arrives hasn't arrived for me
hasn't arrived for any coach that I know
who's actually successful they've
learned to take action
without knowing how the outcome's going
to be and they're willing to embrace the
risk and put it out there
and so that needs to become your focus
is how can I start to do more risky
Behavior
if you're unwilling to take risk if
you're if you're unwilling to put
yourself out there just to see what
happens
then you need to ask yourself why is
that
what is what is underneath the surface
that is preventing this from happening
and when you start to become aware of
that
things will start to fall in place for
you you'll be willing to pick an idea or
two to test out for a niche
you'll be what will actually happen is
you'll be more open to
things turning out better for you and we
have to stop Imagining the worst case
scenario we need to start Imagining the
best case scenario how things are going
to go our brain doesn't need any help to
make up and imagine the worst case
scenario in any situation
but we need to flip it when that happens
now it's having this happen this
afternoon I started thinking man I'm
gonna like my brain literally was
telling me my business is going to die
I'm going to lose customers without
making enough money I had to shift it
out of that state because I started
getting depressed I started getting
angry I started feeling like a failure
and I had to intentionally say no this
is that's like why am I focusing on that
right there no truth there's literally
no evidence in my life that there was
any truth behind that worry by the way
oh
and and and yet that's where my brain
went
and so that doesn't stop no matter how
much success you have your brain will
not stop trying to convince you that
things are going to go bad for you
so stop waiting until it finally does
you have to learn to shift your thoughts
shift them into the direction of
Imagining the best case scenario and
then take action on it
and ultimately we cannot worry what
anybody thinks about us we cannot
concern our energy with anybody's
opinions of us I made a post recently
that offended quite a few people
that was about the fact that
in my business
um people over the age of 60 generally
don't become a client of mine
but I got a lot of people over 60 who
follow me now there's some outliers but
in that I'm gonna stop targeting people
over 60 with my advertising
because I lose money every single time
we get a lot of cheap leads and they all
go in the toilet nobody buys anything in
that age category
that could be offensive to somebody
I you know I I'm
not that's not my concern my concern is
how can I be profitable in my business
what what's the activities I need to do
to actually make a profit in my business
okay
and so if I know okay people under 60
are more likely to become a client of
mine through advertising and I'm putting
money into advertising I'm going to do
what's most profitable for my business
even though I know that I could help
that group of people
stop
doing things
quote unquote because you're trying to
do the right thing
just stop it
do what's profitable in your business
learn to sell
learn to give a presentation learn to
make a connection with people grow in
your people skills grow in your
communication ability to be able to
communicate with people and to be able
to get people to give you their credit
card to pay for the solution and the
transformation that they want that
behavior right there of being able to
attract people that want you to solve a
problem for them
and then you strategically provide them
that solution for payment
creates a highly successful highly
profitable mentoring coaching Mastermind
business
there's no other Behavior other than
that now the nuances could be your
funnel building and and getting people
on your email list and doing the
presentation but it's all those are just
tools to be able to make a connection
with the people that are most likely to
spend money with you
they're the best tools to be able to do
so
but we need to not get so caught up in
the process
and and the minutia of doing all that
perfect and focus on the end goal
connection with people that have
problems to lead them to their solution
that's our Focus
we cannot I you know I had somebody
nitpicking over a comment that I made on
social media today
guarantee you she's not making any money
in her business
um about how wrong I was to say that
you're gonna have a really hard time if
you're trying to monetize a non-profit
or get really like people that don't
have money to invest with you to try to
get them to and make an investment with
you
and then what I said was focus on what's
most profitable for your business and
then pour those profits into the
non-profit area she didn't like that
she's like what so you know
fundraisers don't work I'm like what are
you what are you talking about it's just
kept going on like trying to nitpick
over what I said almost like have a good
day
not my job not my problem to now come
down to that level of energy with people
honestly People's Energy
isn't a very low State most of the time
and for you to be able to be successful
in your coaching business you have to
keep it at an elevated State a level
where you you're operating you're flying
high above in the clouds above where
most people are operating well isn't
that arrogant isn't that rude no it's
not at all in fact
I I actually have more compassion and
can help people better
and I don't sugarcoat the truth when I
operate from that level you know
my family has made
tens of millions of dollars my mom added
up
over 100 million dollars
puts us in the point the top
0.1 percent
uh income earners category
and
at that level like there's a different
game that's that's being played then
then most people
are even willing to talk about
and
for you to be able to raise your income
to a level where you're making ten
thousand twenty thousand thirty thousand
dollars a month you have to raise your
state and your awareness
and you're going to operate differently
than 99 of everybody in your life
everybody that you ever met before
everybody that you know
you're going to have to do behaviors
that go against
how you've been raised what you've been
taught for years
but when you start doing that
intentionally and you make that actually
part of your process
listen you're gonna have people telling
you that that the things that you're
doing in your business are wrong
they're not going to work that you
shouldn't be doing them
and you need to just keep doing them and
you just keep doing those things and
stop letting people sway you away from
taking action because you're concerned
about being wrong and doing the right
thing in your business
don't let anybody tell you how to run
your business unless they're a mentor
that you look up to that has a track
record of success my track record is
creating eight figure
mentoring businesses coaching businesses
and so what I'm telling you right now is
the foundation of what will transition
you from where you're at
to success when you shift out of the
State of Mind of somebody who's just
going through the motions who's a
complainer who's a whiner who has the
victim mindset
and you step into abundance and you
start to realize I have all the
resources that I need to be successful
I'm going to keep my vision focused on
the bright side of the best case
scenario of how things can go and I'm
going to start to take action even if I
can't control the outcome even if it's a
mistake I'm going to be a hundred
percent okay with doing the wrong thing
just to see what happens just to
experiment just to gather data to see
how people are going to respond and I'm
not going to let the outcome Slow Me
Down
from continuing that work continuously
and and no matter what happens in the
outcome
I'm not gonna pause for an extended
length of time to quote unquote recover
I'm gonna keep going I'm gonna keep
moving forward and that my friends is
Gonna Make You Unstoppable okay so
hopefully this has helped you hopefully
this is
lit a fire under you that was my goal
with this
and I can't wait to see you be
successful listen if you're not part of
my client growth accelerator jump on the
waiting list get on the waiting list of
my coaching program we're helping
mentors coaches trainers create
multi-six figure businesses walking them
through step by step every single aspect
of what it takes we have training
resources I'm in there supporting you
personally
every single week to help you I'm
responding
in the group I'm responding to your
sales copy I'm helping you put it all
together so that you're not stuck and so
most of the time the doors are not open
to our program you can get on the
waiting list and when we do open those
doors
it's going to be one of the best
investments you've ever made in your
life and I can't wait to see you in
there with us
talk soon grow your life everybody have
a good one
[Music]
foreign